D2.
Amy wrote a letter for an Indian rhino.
Read it below.
Dear Humans, I am an Indian rhino.
I live in northern India.
I eat grass and small plants.
I am writing to ask for your help to protect the rhinos in the wild.
Many years ago, thousands of us lived in some parts of Asia.
We ate special plants near our homes, but they became fewer and fewer when farmers started using them to feed their animals.
People also hunted us for our horns.
As a result, our numbers started to drop.
The governments of India and Nepal made laws to protect us, but you can do more.
Please stop using our horns for your own needs.
Our horns are important for us to live healthy lives.
Please help us, or there may be none of us left in the future.
Thank you for reading my letter, yours sincerely, Laila, an Indian rhino.